http://www.impactfactory.com/privacy-policy

Impact Factory Ltd Privacy Policy
ScopeThis Privacy Policy is effective with respect to any data that we have collected, or collect, about and/or from you. It explains what we do with your personal data, whether we are in the process of booking you on our public courses, continuing our relationship with you once we have attended the course or you are visiting our website. It describes how we collect, use and process your personal data, and how, in doing so, we comply with our legal obligations to you. Your privacy is important to us, and we are committed to protecting and safeguarding your data privacy rights.This Privacy Policy applies to the personal data of our employees, Website Users, course delegates, Clients, Suppliers, and other people whom we may contact in order to deliver training. It also applies to the emergency contacts of our staff.For the purpose of applicable data protection legislation (including but not limited to the General Data Protection Regulation (Regulation (EU) 2016/679) (the "GDPR"), Impact Factory Limited will be what's known as the controller and the Processer of the personal data you provide to us.We do not store customer credit card details.We gather name, address, telephone numbers, email address. For our staff we gather personal data regarding date of birth, immigration status and right to work, NI number and bank detailsIt is important to point out that we may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Accuracy and Retention of Data.We do our best to keep your data accurate and up to date, to the extent that you provide us with the information we need to do so. If your data changes (for example, if you have a new email address), then you are responsible for notifying us of those changes. We will retain your information for as long as needed to provide you with our Services. We may also retain and use your information in order to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, prevent abuse, and enforce our Agreements.Access RightsWe will give an individual access to any Personal Information we hold about them within 30 days of any request for that information. Individuals may request to access, correct, amend or delete information we hold about them by contacting us. Unless it is prohibited by law, we will remove any Personal Information about an individual from our servers at your or their request. There is no charge for an individual to access or update their Personal Information.BreachesWe take reasonable and appropriate measures to protect Personal Information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction, taking into account the risks involved in the processing and the nature of the Personal Information If a security breach causes an unauthorized intrusion into our system that materially affects the personal data we hold on you then Impact Factory will notify you as soon as possible and later report the action we took in response.
